aol.in 2010-01-07

# AOL India - Privacy Policy

**AOL INDIA PRIVACY POLICY**  
When you register with and use AOL India, you gain access to the enhanced websites, services and other content and offerings from AOL Interactive Media India Private Limited ("AOL India") and its affiliates (collectively, "AOL"). When you register with AOL, you provide personally identifiable information (your "AOL India information"). This Policy explains the information practices that apply to your AOL India information, as well as the choices you can make about the ways this information is used by AOL.

Registering to use your Screen Name with AOL is optional. This Privacy Policy applies only to information AOL collects about you as a user of AOL India. This policy does not apply to information about you collected by AOL's affiliated providers, such as, AOL.com, or third party Web sites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from AOL India. The information collected or received by AOL's affiliated providers and these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Collection of your AOL India Information**

Your AOL India information consists of personally identifiable information collected or received about you when you interact with AOL India's Web sites, services and offerings as a registered user. Depending on how you use the service, your AOL India information may include:  
\- registration-related information (such as name, home or work addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone and fax numbers, birth date or gender);  
\- information about your visits to AOL India Web sites and pages, and your responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on these Web sites and pages;  
\- information about the searches you perform through AOL India and how you use the results of those searches;  
\- information about AOL India services or offerings that you use, and how frequently you use them;  
\- information about how long you have used services from AOL India prior to registering with the service;  
\- transaction-related information (such as credit card or other preferred means of payment, billing or shipping information, or a history of products purchased through AOL India);  
\- customer service information about you as a AOL India user or subscriber; or  
\- other information specifically related to your use of a particular AOL India service or offering.

**Your AOL India information may be supplemented with additional information from other companies.**

Your AOL India information may also include certain technical information gathered or received when you use AOL India. Some of the technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), CPU type, your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; information about the version of service from an AOL affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; other information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider. Your AOL India information may be collected and stored on AOL servers or servers of such other subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf, located in the United States, the territory of India and such other countries as we may disclose from time to time. Additionally, AOL India will use the AOL Screen Name Service, or similar technologies, to authenticate you on AOL India and enable you to take advantage of AOL India's offerings. You can learn more about other benefits of the Screen Name Service, including its ability to facilitate your use of Web sites outside AOL India, by visiting [Screen Name Service](https://my.screenname.aol.com/en-in).

**How Your AOL India information is Used**

Your AOL India information is used  
\- to operate and improve the Web sites, services and offerings available through AOL India;  
\- to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you;  
\- to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;  
\- to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;  
\- to conduct research about your use of AOL India; and  
\- to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

Your AOL India information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a transaction you have requested, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your AOL India information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. AOL may use your AOL India information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers receive aggregate data about groups of AOL India users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.

If you use AOL India communications tools to disclose information about yourself publicly (for example, in chat rooms or online message boards made available by AOL India), other online users may obtain access to any information you provide. The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as an AOL India user, may be accessed and disclosed in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); in other circumstances in which AOL India believes AOL India is being used in the commission of a crime; when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or when necessary either to protect the rights or property of AOL, AOL India or its affiliated providers, or for us to render the service you have requested. AOL India may use agents and contractors in order to help operate the service. If such agents and contractors have access to personally identifiable information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for AOL India.

In the event that ownership of AOL or the AOL India service was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your AOL India information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your AOL India information, AOL will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

**Your Choices About Your AOL India Information**

AOL India provides you with access to your registration and any billing or shipping information; the ability to edit this information at the [My Account](https://my.screenname.aol.com/en-in) area; and the ability to deactivate your registration with AOL India. Additionally, some AOL India services (AOL Search, for example) may offer you the ability to control what information is collected or used when you use these services.

You will be given the opportunity to make choices about how your AOL India information may be used by AOL to make marketing offers to you. Any marketing preferences that you will be able to make will not apply to communications that are directly related to your registration and use of AOL India software and services (including upgrades and updates to the service), or the fulfillment of a specific transaction you have requested (for example, a service advisory from AOL India, or an acknowledgment of a purchase order). 

You may also choose whether AOL's affiliated providers receive personally identifiable AOL India information. This choice does not apply to the sharing of AOL India information necessary to provide you the basic functionality of the service (for example, recognizing you as an authenticated user on affiliated providers' Web sites or services). Additionally, AOL India may share personally identifiable AOL India information with one or more of its affiliated providers when that information is necessary to carry out a specific transaction or request you make for an offering from the service or its affiliated providers, or as otherwise specified at the time you take advantage of that particular service.

Because the choices you make in connection with your AOL India information may not take effect immediately, it is possible you may receive a communication during the period in which your request is being processed.

**Cookies, Web Beacons and Advertisement Networks**

Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as an AOL India user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain AOL India offerings.

AOL India may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in combination with your AOL India information to enhance and personalize your experience on AOL India, including to operate and improve offerings through AOL India; to help authenticate you when you use AOL India; to remember your preferences and registration information; to enable a shopping cart; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of AOL India offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which AOL India e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through AOL India. 

AOL and its advertisers may from time to time use advertising network providers, to help present advertisements on AOL India. These advertising networks use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. AOL may share certain information about you as a user that is not personally identified (such as user age and zip code) with certain advertising network providers in order to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event AOL India utilizes the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks. 

**Our Commitment to Security**

AOL has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your AOL India information, but cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers). To protect your privacy and security, AOL uses passwords to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to any of your AOL India information.

**Special Note for Parents**

AOL India is intended for a general audience. Registration for certain services on AOL India may not be available for children under the age of 13. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about AOL India's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address: [privacyquestions@aol.in](mailto:privacyquestions@aol.in?Subject=AOL%20India%27s%20Privacy%20Policy)

**Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information**

AOL may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to AOL India's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from AOL India, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future. 

_Last Updated April 25, 2008_
